{
    "id": "adad1d0896fe425f8d6c4a53323e258b",
    "title": "General English Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Besides his parents, he …………………… . present at the function.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were",
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The storm was accompanied …………………… . heavy rains.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "by",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Choose the word that is misspelt.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "embarassing",
                "diarrhea",
                "entrepreneur",
                "accustomed"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "‘Sine die’ means",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "die while in service",
                "after the date",
                "indefinitely"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Choose the antonym of the word ‘Embellish’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sacrifice",
                "decorate",
                "disfigure"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "A person who lacks experience can be called a ………………… .",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "veteran",
                "senior",
                "junior",
                "novice"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "I have bought a bag of …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "floor",
                "flour",
                "flower"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You will never win, ………………… .. hard you may try.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "despite",
                "although",
                "however"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Barking dogs ………………… bite.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "seldom",
                "hardly",
                "rarely"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following words has nearly the same meaning as the phrase ‘make out’?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "read",
                "learn",
                "understand"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}